

CONTACT

- hansonsun.school@gmail.com
- 778-836-0421
- www.hanson-sun.github.io
- 543 Main Street, San Francisco, CA 94122

EDUCATION

IB DIPLOMA PROGRAMME

2018 - present

Richmond Secondary School, BC, CA

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership
Analytical Thinking
Teamwork
Logical Thinking
Patience
Problem Solving
Communication

SOCIAL





HANSON SUN

Student

ABOUT

Hanson Sun is an IB Diploma student at Richmond Secondary School. He is passionate about programming and technology. In his free time, he enjoys making fun programming projects and learning new skills. Hanson has experience leading clubs and applying his programming knowledge to real-world projects.

HARD SKILLS

EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER OF MATH CONNECT



May 2020 - Present

- Planned, designed, and launched a free NPO, Math Connect
- Interviewed high school students as potential tutors
- Managed tutors, students, and classes
- Created website, mathconnect.ca

CO-PRESIDENT OF RHS PROGRAMMING CLUB



Jun 2020 - Present

- Created interactive programming curriculum and lessons every week
- Teaches creative programming lessons every week
- Organized school-wide programming competitions and hackathons
- Implemented large scale hackathons (Hack the North) and competitions (CCC)
- Manages and maintains website

PROJECTS

ANALYSIS OF 2D PHYSICS SIMULATIONS IN JAVASCRIPT

Feb 2020

- An implementation of a simple 2D JavaScript physics engine
- https://hanson-sun.github.io/Math-EE/

COLLECTION OF JAVASCRIPT ART

May 2020

- An investigation of programmatic art with p5.js
- https://javascriptart.hansonsun.repl.co/